They had a truck outside with my face on the side of it that said Amanda Seals is a Jew hater.
I am not.
That's crazy.
Yes.
Then they were driving that truck around town.
I actually pulled up on the truck and it was a nigga driving and smoking a blunt.
And I was like.
It was not a blunt.
It was not.
You, Amanda.
I have it on Tate.
Amanda.
I was like.
They bought your soul.
Right.
Because you know that's probably paid for by whoever the hell.
Oh, it absolutely is.
And people, of course, were like.
I mean, he need to get his bag, too.
And I'm like, you see, that's the problem with this nation, though.
That's so crazy.
The fact that y'all be like.
Y'all will do anything for a bag.
For money.
It's crazy.